<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Posts on Chris Whiteley</title>
        <link>https://chriswhiteley.co.uk/posts/</link>
        <description>Recent content in Posts on Chris Whiteley</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://chriswhiteley.co.uk/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        
        <item>
            <title>Setting goals for 2020</title>
            <link>https://chriswhiteley.co.uk/posts/2020/01/setting-goals-for-2020/</link>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            
            <guid>https://chriswhiteley.co.uk/posts/2020/01/setting-goals-for-2020/</guid>
            <description>Over the past couple of years i&#39;ve realised the power of speaking something into existence. This has mainly manifested itself in sporting goals but I think it&#39;s applicable to all areas of life. The accountability that you gain from putting your goals and ambitions out there for the world to see, really can&#39;t be understated. So here are my goals for 2020!
Tech Goals  Release Subtle Sports open-source..This is a project that I started over the summer when the Cricket World Cup was on.</description>
            <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Over the past couple of years i've realised the power of speaking something into existence. This has mainly manifested itself in sporting goals but I think it's applicable to all areas of life. The accountability that you gain from putting your goals and ambitions out there for the world to see, really can't be understated. So here are my goals for 2020!</p>
<h4 id="tech-goals-">Tech Goals</h4>
<ol>
<li><strong>Release Subtle Sports open-source.</strong>.This is a project that I started over the summer when the Cricket World Cup was on. It's a minimal sports tracker that let's you keep tabs on your favourite matches without having BBC Sport open constantly (read: track sports at work). More details to come on this in a future post.</li>
<li><strong>Contribute to an open-source project.</strong> I think it would be great to begin raising my external developer profile by contributing some code to a reputable open-source project. I'm on the hunt for something, any ideas please <a href="mailto:chriswhiteley5@gmail.com?subject=open-source%20contributions">get in touch.</a></li>
</ol>
<h4 id="sporting-goals-">Sporting Goals</h4>
<ol>
<li><strong>5km sub-20 mins.</strong> Starting with the shortest distance, I want to go fast! Sub-20 minutes is the goal. My PB at the beginning of 2020 stands at 21.45 so there is a fair way to go.</li>
<li><strong>10km sub-45 mins.</strong> Moving to a slightly longer distance, I see this a stepping stone to goal 3.</li>
<li><strong>Half-Marathon sub-1hr 45.</strong> I've never run this far before but by the end of this year I want to be aiming to set a good time rather than purely complete the race.</li>
<li><strong>Run 1500km in total.</strong> The aim here is to encourage consistency. Last year I went through weeks/months of fantastic training but then would also have weeks where I do nothing. I want running to be an integral part of my life and setting a high mileage goal encourages me to remain consistent to avoid having to catch up.</li>
<li><strong>Half-Ironman.</strong> Definitely my &ldquo;A-race&rdquo; for 2020. I want to step up to the 70.3 distance. The aim here is mainly completion, but in a respectable time.</li>
</ol>
<h4 id="self-improvement-goals-">Self-Improvement Goals</h4>
<ol>
<li><strong>Improve piano to a standard where I can play in front of people.</strong> I've wanted to pick the piano back up for the longest time, but it's really hard to learn the piano without owning a piano, so at the end of 2019 I bought one to remove that excuse. By the end of 2020 I want to have progressed to the point where I can sit down and play a piece that i'm proud of in front of my friends.</li>
<li><strong>Write 52 blog posts.</strong> I've always loved reading amateur opinion pieces on topics ranging from technology to sport. I find them to be so much more genuine than the media you see from major publications. 1 post a week should be possible.</li>
</ol>
<p>Those are my goals. I'm excited to get started and I guess there will be a round-up post on here at the end of the year to see how i've done.</p>
]]></content>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
